[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
[Disclaimer: Characters, locations, and all depicted events are fictional
and for entertainment purposes only; viewer discretion is advised]
[Your Third Series]
You can stay here and enjoy the vacation.
If something is troubling you,
don't hold it for too long.
You already know
what you should do.
Right.
Did Sarm ask you
to look at a certain box?
A box?
Over there. Right there.
He wants to marry me?
Little...
Do you accept me?
The break is already over.
So why are you still here?
Can I sit with you, then?
Is the food at the engineering cafeteria
not that good?
Why do you always come to eat at the QC cafeteria?
Mm...
They don't serve peas there.
Oh, I see.
Why don't you ask the head chef
to make some pea dishes?
That's because...
The type of pea that I like
is lantao peas.
What should I do, then?
Hm?
Not getting flustered by that.
No need to.
I just want to let you know that I like you,
and I'm hitting on you.
You sure talk a lot.
So,
are you an engineer
or a poet?
I'm an engineer, of course.
An engineer who will mend your heart.
♫What is this? I've never realized♫
♫That someone like you can make my heart race♫
You're cute.
Wasin.
I'm glowing red like tomatoes.
If you don't want to drive yourself crazy,
mind joining me in Wang Nam Khiao District?
We'll watch the sunset together.
Why do you have to be kind to me?
A cat's broken heart
can only be mended by beautiful scenery.
It's so that you can take your eyes off your old crush.
Sure.
I'm still flustered, though.
♫How did someone I never really cared about become like this?♫
♫Turned out this way?♫
No need.
I like it when you're flustered.
Dig in.
I'll keep you company.
♫I don't what to do♫
Sure.
♫'Cause you always know what my heart would say♫
[Your Third Series]
♫I've held back, but you're impossible to resist♫
♫'Cause you make me wanna kiss, kiss♫
♫Never thought I'd fall for you♫
♫Accidentally gave you my heart♫
♫Wanna be close to you, can you tell me if this is love?♫
♫It feels so right, should I let my heart take control?♫
♫You're too cute, you drive me crazy♫
♫Just a glance from you almost melts me, baby♫
♫Can I give a cutie like you a kiss?♫
♫Can I give you one more kiss?♫
♫You♫
♫Just a bit more♫
♫Can I kiss you one more time?♫
♫Can I give you one more kiss?♫
♫I'm not gonna lie♫
♫If I can't kiss you now, I'd lose my mind♫
♫You, ou, ou, ou♫
♫You, ou, ou, ou, ou♫
♫If I can't kiss you now, I'd lose my mind♫
♫Can I give a cutie like you a kiss?♫
♫Can I give you one more kiss?♫
♫You♫
♫Just a bit more♫
♫Can I kiss you one more time?♫
♫Can I give you one more kiss?♫
♫I'm not gonna lie♫
♫If I can't kiss you now, I'd lose my mind♫
♫You, ou, ou, ou♫
[Your Third Series]
Up until now,
I have only dedicated myself to work and studies.
For this project, please take care of
this and that part for me.
- No problem. - Alright.
Thank you.
I never imagined myself getting married.
You'll finally get married now, huh?
But if that person is Sarm,
I have no doubts.
Though we feel the same way,
getting to this point
was not easy at all.
I am starving.
I still have not found the target.
Whatever,
I will take this as a vacation, I guess.
♫Sneaking a look from afar, I'm not so sure♫
♫Seems like the target isn't yet aware♫
How ridiculous can working as an assistant get,
I wonder?
♫When the sun sets,♫
♫Our eyes finally meet♫
♫A white beach,♫
♫Just you and me♫
♫The longer I gaze, the more my heart races♫
It accumulates
little...
by little.
We eventually grew closer.
On my first visit to Adisuan Farm,
I came here to work.
But this time...
it feels like returning home.
Are you ready
to get married?
It is too late for me to say no now.
That's everything, right?
He makes me feel...
loved.
When I look into his eyes, I see the word...
forever.
Mm.
Let us go.
If either couple starts fighting,
make them sleep in the stable.
- Mm. - Shall we?
Hey, what about you?
When will you have...
Hm?
Like they do?
What makes you think that I don't?
[Payu: Are you available tomorrow? We need to talk. Song: Yes, I am
Allow us to take our leave.
Mm.
Well then...
I'd like to take my leave as well.
Mm.
Oh, Dad.
You want to leave?
Yeah.
Bye-bye, Dad.
Right.
Sarm?!
Hey.
Dad is watching us.
Like an iron steed.
Go harder! Even harder!
Sarm...
Put me down gently. You scared me.
Gosh.
My spouse gets scared easily, doesn't he?
You never stop calling me that, do you?
Come on.
I want the whole world to know
that I've finally
got a spouse!
You are waking everyone up.
They are sleeping, you know?
What was that?
Well...
I want someone genuine
who
kisses me back when I do,
to keep things fair.
Maybe the person is right there?
Gosh.
You're this adorable.
I've totally fallen for you and no one else.
I'm done being a tiger now.
Do you want to be my prey instead?
I'll be a tiny chick
in the palm of your hand.
Very small.
You are this tiny.
So, so tiny.
Tomorrow is the day.
I won't let you change your mind now.
It is no one else
but you, Sarm.
Okay, you're good to go now.
Thank you very much.
Alright. If you'll excuse me.
Right.
Am I really getting married?
It does hurt for real...
Jam.
Oh, Little Jam!
You look really adorable today.
You're the cutest of them all.
You're so adorable everywhere.
You look cute from this side, too.
You really do.
Wow.
Try saying that I do not.
Oh, Little Jam.
Do you know
that's the hardest thing for me to say in my entire life?
That's because you look adorable every day.
You look cute when you're angry,
when you're mad,
and even when you're upset.
You just can't stop looking so adorable.
You look so cute that
I want to kiss you.
Take a seat.
Wait until they call us.
I love you, Little Jam.
I love you, too, Sarm.
It's almost time...
It's almost time.
Are you ready?
I am ready.
Let's go.
Don't forget about the blazer.
Wish you a ton of happiness.
The same goes for you, Jam.
Thank you.
We're already happy, aren't we?
Right?
May it be even happier.
Take it more seriously, Sarm.
Can't you see?
I am always serious.
Be serious.
♫You're the dream, that I've been waiting to come true,♫
♫Flourishing into a beautiful love with you♫
♫You're my guiding light when I'm all alone♫
♫That's who you are, the love that nothing will ever come close♫
♫You're the one truth♫
♫That always warms my heart♫
So sweet.
Another hand.
Calm down, Sarm.
There goes the mighty tiger of Pak Chong.
Little Jam,
no need.
Just put it on.
Right.
- Kiss now, kiss now, kiss now. - Kiss, kiss, kiss.
- Kiss him, kiss, him, kiss him. - Kiss now, kiss now, kiss now.
♫You always warm my heart♫
♫You are the one♫
May your life be full of happiness.
May your life go smoothly from now on.
I'm delighted
to have you as my son-in-law, Jam.
Thank you, Dad.
Sit down and talk things through
whenever an issue comes up.
So emotional.
Ridiculous.
Thank you very much.
Thank you, Mr. Sib.
What?
You're so happy that you cried?
Oh, uh...
They left me behind as the only single person now.
Oh, I'm proud, then.
Right.
- Shouldn't you feel sorry, Dad? - Dad!
Oh, just kidding.
Congratulations, Sarm and Mr. Jam.
Thank you.
- Thank you. - Thank you, everyone.
Mm.
Getting to the good part now?
I'll stay outside.
Come on.
Let's leave them to it
- so that they can enjoy the moment, - Right.
shall we?
Okay.
- Let's go. - Follow me, sons.
Bye-bye, everyone.
- Come on, let's go. - Make sure you break the bed.
Bye-bye, everybody.
Thank you
for choosing me.
You were not a choice I made.
You were a discovery.
Oh, Jam...
I will tear you to shreds.
You never take anything seriously.
I'm serious.
[One month later]
Sarm...
Sarm.
I can kiss you all day, you know?
Hm?
I need to go to work.
Little Jam,
today's Saturday.
I am heading to the shop.
New items come in today.
Okay.
If that's the case,
I'll join you at lunch
so that we can have a good time at a different place.
Having lunch at a different place?
No.
A different place
for enjoying my spouse.
Ow...
I...I think we should dig in.
Sarm, take a seat.
Okay.
Sure thing.
Thank you.
I have a meeting with Ms. Vibhavadi at noon.
You never have time for me.
Oh, Sarm...
It is not like that.
I mean,
you should try the stew.
I made it myself.
Whoa, five-spice stew with braised pork.
Really? You made it yourself?
Oh, is there a yogurt drink?
Do we have any?
You do not get to to have it today.
Your sugar intake is already too high.
Fine...
Whatever my spouse says.
Good boy.
Your cheeks are way sweeter anyway.
One more time.
One more...
By the way, my fists
are second to none.
Oh...
Want some?
I prefer this.
It doesn't hurt either.
We might as well skip this meal.
Just a little more.
We are in a dining room,
not a battlefield.
But with you,
wherever you are,
it's a "battlefield of love."
Did you come up with that yourself
or did you take it from a series?
I came up with it myself.
That's because
the inspiration behind that phrase is you.
- Let me have you one more time. - Whoa...
Oh!
The food is getting cold at this point.
Huh?
- We can eat it later if we want to. - At this point...
Hey.
Don't overwork yourself, okay?
Call me if you're tired.
Understood?
Right.
I have my personal consultant.
Of course.
It's me,
the spouse of the year,
right?
You are claiming the title yourself, are you not?
Hey.
Thank you
for moving in with me completely.
Your house is also mine.
Bye-bye.
Kiss, kiss.
I will be going now.
- Bye-bye. - Bye-bye.
Little Jam,
I love you.
- I love you, too. - Bye-bye.
Bye-bye.
Do miss me, okay?
All the time.
Here's a kiss.
Mwah, mwah.
Love you.
Alright.
I'm going to kiss a puppy,
a kitten,
and even a starfish.
Mwah, mwah.
♫Kiss, kiss, kiss, kiss, kiss♫
♫This kiss is for you♫
♫Ju Bu Ju Bu Ju Bu Jub♫
Ow, this is killing me.
Alright...
Come here.
Take a seat, Jam.
I'll give you a massage.
Where are you feeling sore?
Here.
Here?
So good...
Actually,
hugging you already makes me feel better.
Oh...
So are you tired or feeling sore?
I want my spouse
to live comfortably.
I actually want you to take it easy on your work.
I do not like being unoccupied.
If so,
we should have an eye-to-eye conversation.
Can we instead change it to
a your-hand-on-my-shoulder conversation?
Oh,
you want your body to feel good, no?
Oh...
Of course, it is you who are giving me the massage.
I'm serious, though.
Maybe you have...
actually been overworking.
But things are going well.
If that's the case,
how about this?
On weekdays,
work as much as you like,
but on the weekends,
consider spending time with your family.
Would it be a good idea?
Of course.
Do you know that your extremely adorable,
handsome,
and perfect spouse
is waiting to do activities together?
What activities?
I have already tried all of the rides at Adisuan Farm.
Oh.
I've got so many games for you to play,
like
waking up a big worm,
milking a so-called cow,
or,
kneading some bouncy buns.
I've still got so much more.
You're too obsessed, Sarm.
What?
I just want to have you. That's all.
I want to have you
day and night.
We were just hugging each other to sleep last night.
Mm.
Last night is now a past.
What matters is tonight.
I think...
we should save our hugs for tomorrow morning
before heading to work.
It feels exciting that way.
If that's the case,
can I kiss you right now
at least one time?
Please?
Shall we hit the shower?
Do you want to shower first
or should I go first?
You're supposed to ask
if we want to take a rain shower
or take a warm bath.
That should be the question.
Who says I am going to shower with you?
Come on, Little Jam.
You are the only one imagining it.
I'm telling you that right now.
Sarm.
Let me take care of you tonight,
okay?
Mm.
Why are you staring at me so much?
What?
Why are you this adorable, then?
Little Jam.
Do you love me, though?
I do.
You're more than love to me.
What about you?
Do you love me?
I also love you.
I'm sorry?
Didn't catch that.
What did you say?
I said, "I love you," alright?
Oh, you're so sweet, my good boy.
Listen.
From this day onward,
there won't be a day
that I don't love you.
How about a session before the shower?
Sarm...
What are you watching?
Sarm.
Look at this YouTuber eating a durian.
- It looks so tasty. - Whoa...
You want a durian?
Mm!
I want it!
If you do,
what do you have to do first?
Refreshing.
Sure.
I'll deliver.
New and Jiew,
durian!
New and Jiew.
Whoa...
Thank you, New and Jiew.
Oh...
You are amazing, Sarm.
Of course,
there's nothing that your spouse cannot do.
Let me just tell you that
I can do everything
under the sun.
You are just too much!
By the way...
do you know how to open a durian?
When it comes to this,
don't worry.
New and Jiew.
Whoa...
It won't take long.
I cannot wait.
New and Jiew.
Thank you very much.
Looks just as tasty as the one in the video.
Of course.
This durian has a great shape
and a beautiful color
and it is perfectly formed.
Another bite?
Mm.
That's better.
Is it sweet?
Hm.
It is so tasty.
I want to have it every day.
You can,
but you have to exercise, too.
Can I exercise later?
I will do it later.
Sure.
However,
I do feel like...
I deserve a reward.
What should be the reward?
Anything will do.
It's all fine by me.
If you behave and be a good boy,
I will consider it.
Let it last all night, okay?
Do not be the first to go out of breath, then.
I won't.
Let's go!
Let us go!
Days off spent together
do not have to be extraordinary.
Just durians,
laughter,
and somebody by my side are simply enough.
I feel so relaxed.
Of course.
I have a back pain, too.
See?
All you do is work.
You never exercise.
How much does it hurt?
Not much.
But it feels a bit uncomfortable.
Right here.
Well then,
I'll take you to the doctor tomorrow.
Do not flake out.
Mm.
I will not.
Good boy.
Once we're done,
I'll take you to a yoga class
and a pilates class.
They're good for you.
So do not complain, okay?
At this moment,
anything goes for me.
Okay.
If so,
Let's warm up, shall we?
Warm up?
How exactly?
It's to get our blood pumping.
Then, our muscles will relax.
They'll be refreshed and firm.
You always
find ways to come back to this topic.
I want to take care of my spouse, alright?
Please.
Are you sure?
Tonight, I'll do my best to follow your lead.
Doing this kind of workout every night
will surely
get rid of your back pain.
Sarm.
Though you're always thirsty,
you always treat me so well.
My spouse needs to be healthy
so that we can be together forever.
Sarm.
Huh?
Let me do it.
Sarm...
Babe.
Someone was trying to flirt with me today.
It's that guy
dressed up as a caveman spirit.
While I'm away,
do not wander off on your own, okay?
Miss him, don't you?
I will tease you back.
Do you know that
a good spouse
is the one who wears a fluffy tail?
Sarm.
Let us go.
♫What is this? I've never realized♫
♫That someone like you can make my heart race♫
♫I just have to believe that that person is you♫
♫How did someone I never really cared about♫
♫Turned out this way?♫
♫Never thought I'd fall for you,♫
♫But I totally did♫
♫Explain how♫
♫You became someone who I trust♫
♫I don't know what to do♫
♫'Cause you always know what my heart would say♫
♫Explain how♫
♫You became someone who I trust♫
♫I don't know what to do♫
♫'Cause you always know what my heart would say♫
[Your Third Series]